[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'もっていきます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "持って行きます"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'もってきます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "持って来ます"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんぱいします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "心配します"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんぱい' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "心配"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'こたえます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "答えます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'こたえ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "答え"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はきけ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "吐き気"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はきけがします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "吐き気がします"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'せき' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "咳"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'せきがでます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "咳がでます"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おなか' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "お腹"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'は' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "歯"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ねつ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "熱"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'やけど' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "火傷"
    }
]